

Immolcaytercanli@gmail.com | # www.tercanli.com | Immolcay | Immo

Summary_

I'm a Software Engineer mostly focused on Python at EPAM Systems Poland. I have **5+ years** of experience specialising in **full-stack web development**, and I have experience with different cloud providers like **Amazon Web Services (AWS)** and **Google Cloud Platform (GCP)**. I love ***nix based environments** and enjoy customising all of the development cycles and automating stuff. Also, I am interested in devising better **problem-solving methods** for challenging tasks and **learning new technologies**.

Skills

Programming Python, JavaScript, Java, Scala

Web Django, Vue.js, React, Play, Flask, Spring **Others** Linux, Docker, GCP, AWS, Bash, Jenkins

Languages Turkish, English

Work Experience __

EPAM SystemKraków, POLAND

SOFTWARE ENGINEER November 2021 - Present

• Worked for an HR and Workforce Management Solution company

• Contributed to a team develops a chatbot for the companies various products

Tech stack: aiohttp (Python), Socket.io for Python (WebSocket), Docker

• Contributed a team develops a tool to manage HR tasks

Tech stack: Django (Python), Docker

Urla Digital Agriculture

Urla, İzmir, TURKEY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER June 2020 - October 2021

Developed software and the hybrid infrastructure for IoT devices (Raspberry Pi) that automate the controlled-environment agriculture
 Tech stack: Python, Docker, Amazon Web Services (like Lambda, RDS, SQS, SNS, DynamoDB, CloudWatch, S3, SES, Timestream, Kinesis Firebose)

• Developed a dashboard to configure, update, and control IoT devices (Raspberry Pi) remotely

Tech stack: Django (Python), MySQL, SQLite, Docker

Linovi Urla, İzmir, TURKEY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER December 2017 - June 2020

Developed and maintained web services that serve as chatbots (Jira, Asana, GitHub, Zendesk, Salesforce, Pagerduty) for Google Chat.
Tech stack: Play (Scala), React (Javascript), MySQL, Redis, Jenkins, Google Cloud Platform (like AppEngine, Compute Engine, Cloud Pub/Sub, Stackdriver)

• Developed a dashboard for an autonomous driving software company

Tech stack: Vert.x (Java), React (JavaScript), Amazon Web Services

• Contributed a Software as a Service called Asena for an information security firm

Tech stack: Spring (Java), Angular.js (JavaScript), Flask (Python), Redmine

Education & Certificates

EDUCATION

Muğla Sıtkı Koçman University

Muğla, TURKEY

COMPUTER ENGINEERING *GPA*: 3.52 / 4.00 September 2012 - June 2017

CERTIFICATES

2017, Jan CCNA R&S: Routing and Switching Essentials, Cisco Networking Academy

2016, Jan CCNA R&S: Introduction to Networks, Cisco Networking Academy

2015, Dec Introduction to Cybersecurity, Cisco Networking Academy

JANUARY 15, 2024 OLCAY TERCANLI · RÉSUMÉ